<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Orders on PrestaShop Specs</title>
    <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Orders on PrestaShop Specs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add new order</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/add.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/add.html</guid>
      <description>Orders &amp;gt; Orders &amp;gt; Add new order
As a merchant, I want to be able to manually add an order to my back-office. Creating a new order is divided into 6 steps:
 I. Customer selection with his/her old orders and carts II. Order cart III. Vouchers IV. Address V. Summary VI. Multistore  I. Customer selection To select the customer, the merchant has to type any character chain that is contained in the customer&amp;rsquo;s first name, last name, or email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listing Page</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/listing.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/listing.html</guid>
      <description>SPECS LISTING ORDER PAGE 1. When there are 0 orders [WAINTING FOR DESIGN]
The empty state card appears ONLY when there is no value (by default or created).
2. Header In the header, there is &amp;ldquo;Add new order&amp;rdquo; button allowing to open the form to create a manual order.
3. Top of the listing Settings wheel When clicking on it, 4 options are displayed:
 Export  After clicking on it, the list is exported in CSV format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Page</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/view-page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/orders/orders/view-page.html</guid>
      <description>Specifications for the order view page for 1.7.7 - 2019
User Story: As a merchant, I need to be able to manage all my orders processed on my website. As a merchant, managing my orders is essential for my e-commerce, so I need to be able to:
 Check the order’s products to prepare it Manage the order’s progress, Edit the customer information or send him messages, Print his invoice, Handle payment methods, Follow my shipping through activities, Manage returns and refunds  WHY</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
