<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UI component on PrestaShop Specs</title>
    <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in UI component on PrestaShop Specs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Language-Selector</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/language-selector.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/language-selector.html</guid>
      <description>Spec Language-Selector Language selector - drop-down - Next to the text field, it is displayed when there are several languages installed (disabled languages are displayed in the drop-down). It allows choosing in which language the content of the field.
By default, if the input text is mandatory, then only the default language is expected to be fulfilled.
If the input is displayed in the Front-Office and only the default language is fulfilled, then Front-Office displays for the other languages the text from the default language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progress Bar Modal</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/progress-bar-modal.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/progress-bar-modal.html</guid>
      <description>SPECS Progress Bar Modal  Title - Label Progress bar - Shows the completion progress into a bar with the percentage of completion warning-alert - it displays the last error message in a warning-alert View %x% errors - Button - Opens the Errors log. %x% is the number of errors  Errors log - Lists in the modal all the error messages in a warning-alert Back to processing - Button - Go back to the Progress bat Download errors log (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings Wheel</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/settings-wheel.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/settings-wheel.html</guid>
      <description>SPECS Settings Wheel When clicking on it, 4 options are displayed:
 Export  After clicking on it, the list is exported in CSV format. The export takes into account filters and sorts that have been done
Import  After clicking on it, the is a redirection to the import page in advanced parameters
Show SQL query  After clicking on it, the SQL query is displayed in a modal. The SQL query takes into account filters and sorts that have been done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Selector Modal</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/shop-selector-modal.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/ui-component/shop-selector-modal.html</guid>
      <description>SPECS Shop Selector Modal  Title Choose a store - Search bar - Search a shop List of stores segmented by group:  Color of the store Store name    Once the store is selected, it continues the previous action with shop context</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
