<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Order Messages on PrestaShop Specs</title>
    <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Order Messages on PrestaShop Specs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add or Edit Order Messages</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages/add-edit-order-message.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages/add-edit-order-message.html</guid>
      <description>SELL &amp;gt; CUSTOMER SERVICE &amp;gt; Order Messages &amp;gt; Add / Edit Order Message&#xA;This UI shows the Order Message adding or editing form.&#xA;Top UI section of Adding or Editing message Multishop switcher - it is an ability to switch the available multistores while being on the current Order messages editing page, and to view the shop Front-Office homepage by redirection. Breadcrumbs, page title, Recommended modules and Help CTA&amp;rsquo;s - default Prestashop UI in the top position, helping administrators to improve the navigation - to view the current Title of the page, see the level of the navigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order Messages</title>
      <link>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages/order-messages.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://build.prestashop.com/prestashop-specs/1.7/back-office/customer-service/order-messages/order-messages.html</guid>
      <description>SELL &amp;gt; CUSTOMER SERVICE &amp;gt; Order Messages&#xA;This UI shows the list of messages, that were sent by webshop customer, who created an Order. By default, Delay message is already created in the list.&#xA;Top UI section Multishop switcher - it is an ability to switch the available multistores while being on the current Order messages editing page, and to view the shop Front-Office homepage by redirection. Add new order message CTA button - this button, with plus icon (+), initiates the redirection to a new page, where a separate Order message creation form is displayed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
